module.exports = [
  {
    question: 'Which of the following is NOT an effective way to kill a vampire?', 
    a: 'Burning',
    b: 'Holy Water',
    c: 'Sunlight',
    d: 'Suffocation',
    answer: 'd'
  },
  {
    question: 'Which actor was famous for playing the part of Doctor Van Helsing?', 
    a: 'Christopher Lee',
    b: 'Bela Lugosi',
    c: 'Peter Cushing',
    d: 'Ian McKellen',
    answer: 'c'
  },
  {
    question: 'What was the original name for candy corn used in the late 1800s?', 
    a: 'Chicken Feed',
    b: 'Wax Fingers',
    c: 'Little Jellies',
    d: 'Wax Plugs',
    answer: 'a'
  },
  {
    question: 'Which of following is NOT one of the seven "Princes of Hell" nor associated with any of the seven deadly sins?', 
    a: 'Lucifier',
    b: 'Leviathan',
    c: 'Beelzebub',
    d: 'Kali',
    answer: 'd'
  },
  {
    question: 'Who wrote the story "The Legend of Sleepy Hollow?"', 
    a: 'Washington Irving',
    b: 'HG Wells',
    c: 'Bram Stoker',
    d: 'Edgar Allen Poe',
    answer: 'a'
  },
  {
    question: 'What is the most well known treatise on witchcraft?', 
    a: 'The Confession of Ellemar',
    b: 'From the Far Reaches of Hell',
    c: 'Malleus Maleficarum',
    d: 'The Satanic Bible',
    answer: 'c'
  },
  {
    question: 'Gargoyles were used to frighten intruders from the buildings they guard, but they also served as what?', 
    a: 'Rainspouts',
    b: 'Chimneys',
    c: 'Lanterns',
    d: 'Lookouts',
    answer: 'a'
  },
  {
    question: 'According to a 1902 supernatural short story by WW Jacobs, which item can grant 3 wishes but at a cost for interfering with fate?', 
    a: 'Dandelion',
    b: 'Monkey Paw',
    c: 'Dragon Ball',
    d: 'Coin',
    answer: 'b'
  },
  {
    question: 'The jack-o-lantern was named after which Jack?', 
    a: 'Jack Skellington',
    b: 'Stingy Jack',
    c: 'Jack the Ripper',
    d: 'Jack Black',
    answer: 'b'
  },
  {
    question: 'What is a man who practices witchcraft called?', 
    a: 'Wizard',
    b: 'Warlock',
    c: 'Witch Doctor',
    d: 'Male Witch',
    answer: 'b'
  },
];